University of Connecticut, Centennial Coordinating Committee Records 1981.0003
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
University of Connecticut, Centennial Coordinating Committee Records
undated, 1964-1981
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
1981.0003
1 Linear Feet
The Centennial Coordinating Committee was responsible for the extensive planning of the university of Connecticut's centennial celebration. The official observance of its 100th anniversary began 23 September 1980. William C. Orr served as chairman of the committee from its inception in 1979 to a successful conclusion at the Ninety-Eighth Annual Commencement, 24 May 1981.
Access
The collection is open and available for research.
Acquisition Information
The records were transferred to the Historical Manuscripts and Archives Division (now Archives & Special Collections) of the University of Connecticut Libraries in November 1981.
History
The Centennial Coordinating Committee was responsible for the extensive planning of the university of Connecticut's centennial celebration. The official observance of its 100th anniversary began 23 September 1980. William C. Orr served as chairman of the committee from its inception in 1979 to a successful conclusion at the Ninety-Eighth Annual Commencement, 24 May 1981.
Scope and Content
The Centennial Coordinating Committee Records are divided into two sections. The first section is the working files of the committee. It includes progress reports, discussions, correspondence, minutes of meetings, and program ideas. The second section contains materials pertaining to various schools and divisions of the University.
Education; Universities and colleges; Notes; Publications (documents); Correspondence; Storrs (inhabited place); Administrative records; Anniversaries; History; Connecticut (state); University of Connecticut
- Series I: Committee Records, undated, 1964-1981
  - Working records
    - Budget worksheets, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Campus Decorations, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Centennial Ball, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Centennial Calendar/timetables, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Centennial Celebration committee, formation of, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Centennial Celebration at other institutions, undated (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
    - Centennial Colloquia Research Foundation, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Centennial Coordinating Committee, 1979 March - September (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Centennial Coordinating Committee correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Centennial Medallion, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Centennial Program, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Centennial Program Ideas, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Centennial Special Events, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Centennial Times, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Class of 1881, search for descendants, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Commencement, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Opening Convocation, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Second Century Convocation, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Convocations, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Early Discussion, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Exhibitions, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Founders Day, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - "Frontiers of the future" media coverage, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - "Frontiers of the future" Planning background, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - "Frontiers of the future" program, publicity, arrangements, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Government (state and federal), undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Historical material, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - History of the University (unsuccessful proposal), 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Homecoming, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Lists of names, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Logo (Centennial logo type), undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Media coverage members, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Minutes, 1979, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Newspaper Supplement—correspondence, etc., undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Orr, William C.—Chairman's notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Parents Day, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Planning progress reports, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Promotion, materials, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Promotion, media group, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Publications, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Selected campus publications, undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Storrs Family and Reunion, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - TV Film "The Storrs Story", undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - UConn 25th Anniversary, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - UN Week, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Schools and Divisions, undated
    - Agriculture and Natural Resources, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Allied Health Professions, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Alumni, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Athletics, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Board of Trustees, undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Branches, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Business Administration, undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Center for Instruction, Media and Technology, undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Education, undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Engineering, undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Extended and Continuing Education, undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Fine Arts, undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Graduate School, undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Health Center, undated (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Home Economics and Family Studies, undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Jorgensen Auditorium, undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Law, undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Liberal Arts and Sciences, undated (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Library, undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Nursing, undated (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Pharmacy, undated (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Social/Recreation, undated (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Social Work, undated (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Student Affairs and Services, undated (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - William Benton Museum of Art, undated (Box 2, Folder 71)